<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="4"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[The Hidden Library



















































                                                          By



                                           Andromeda Team



                                            (Documentation)]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[About our Project


               The Hidden Library is a github project developed in JavaScript. We used

               ExpressJS and MongoDB for Database. The idea behind our project is to
               create a site where the users could share pdf books for free. Our aim is
               to build a simple, but effective platform where the users have the
               potention not only to upload and download books, but to white
               summaries, to rate them. The project is relatively small, but it have a real
               target - to give a posibility for the publishers and active readers.






































               The Library includes many books in all gendres


                 such as Horror, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy and


                                                      more…



                   Registration is fast and easy to do – in less


                  than a minute you can add new books, edit


                                            and delete them.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[How to use The Hidden Library


               1. In order to add a new book, first you have to press Register button

               and complete the registration.

               2. You can delete and edit information about your books but you are not
               allowed to operate with other books!

               3. Complete all the information about each book in correct form!

               4. You can download books for free, without any registration.

               5. The administrator can operate with all the books, which includes

               editing and deleting!

               6. Please, do not add any books without a permission. The author rights
               are checked very strictly!

               7. For more information you can check About our Project.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[How to add a new book


















































                                                     The End]]></page></pages></Search>